(ﾆｰﾅ･ﾄﾞﾗﾝｺﾞ)
うわ～ すてきな場所ね｡
What a beautiful place.
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワァ～！
クワッ クワッ クワッ クワッ…｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)ああっ！
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワァ～！ クワッ？
Mother.
(ｴﾙ)お母さん？
(ｼｬﾘｵｽ17世)時が来れば➡
When the time comes, the seal
will be broken,
エイボスの封印を解き
また こいつを撃つしかない｡
and I will have to fire this once again.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
なぜ俺は 生きようとする…｡
Why am I trying to stay alive?
ここから出せ｡
Let me out of here.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)何度言っても同じことだ｡
ガブリエル様の…｡
The answer remains the same.
Lady Gabriel-
(ｴﾙ)ガブリエルの言うことなんて
聞いてもダメだよ｡
Listening to Gabriel will get you nowhere.
Gabriel cannot save the world.
(ｴﾙ)
ガブリエルに世界は救えない｡➡
救えるのは➡
The only one who can save it...
僕だ｡
is me.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)
んっ んっ んっ… ぷはぁ～！
クワァ～｡
Why... why can't anybody understand?
誰も…
なんで誰も分からないんだ｡
お母さんまで…｡
Not even you, Mother.
(ｴﾙ)ああ～！
クワッ？➡
El seems a little upset by something.
エル君
なんクワァ荒れてますけど？
What? Don't worry about him.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)あっ？ ほっとけ ほっとけ｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワァ～｡
≪やっほ～い 来たよ～！
(２人)ん？
I'm here!
This is not a playground.
(ﾘﾄﾞ)ここは遊び場じゃない｡
あい 分かってます！
I know, I know!
ありがと 天使ちゃん｡
(ﾘﾄﾞ)私の名前は天使じゃない｡➡
Thank you, angel.
My name is not Angel. It is Ridwan.
リド｡
はい 了解です｡
またね リドちゃん！
Copy that!
See you later, Ridwan!
ム～ガ～ロ～ちゃん！
元気だった？
Mugaro!
How have you been?
I'd leave him alone if I were you.
(ﾊﾝｻ)
構わない方がいいクワァもですよ｡
クワァ…｡
This looks just like Bacchus' carriage.
なんか ここ
バッカスの馬車みたい｡
Speaking of the carriage, I hope Hippogriff is doing well.
馬車といえば ヒッポグリフは
元気だといいですが…｡
Hippogriff is! I mean, we came here together after all.
元気だよ｡ だって ヒッポと一緒に
ここまで来たんだもん｡
Really? I'm surprised you made it through the barrier.
(ﾊﾝｻ)ほう～
よく結界を越えられましたね｡
Barrier? You mean that lightning?
結界？ あの雷のこと？
For that, Granny just threw us,
and it was over when I came to.
あれだったら
ばあちゃんに ぶん投げられて➡
目が覚めたら終わってたよ｡
クワァ…
全く意味が分クワァりません｡
I have no idea what you're talking about.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)思い出すぜ
ここを飛び出したあの日のことを｡
That reminds me of the day
we ditched this place.
Really we were just exiled.
追放されただけですけどね｡
なんでバッカスは
神の国を飛び出したの？
Why did you leave the land of the gods,
Bacchus?
Getting worshiped and pampered
as a god wasn't really my style.
ちやほやと崇められる神ってのが
どうにも 俺の性に合わなくてな｡
So I threw it all away and flew off with Hippogriff.
全部放り出して ヒッポグリフと
大空に飛び立ったってわけだ｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワァ～ クワッ クワッ
クワッ クワッ クワッ！
What's so funny?
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)何がおかしい？
それって かっこいいね！
That's so cool!
Right? Hear that, Hamsa?
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)だろ？ ほら見ろ｡
こっち来る？
Wanna come join us?
He talks cool, but he fell head over heels
for this human woman and chased after her.
(ﾊﾝｻ)こんなこと言ってますけど
人間の女性に ひと目ぼれして➡
飛び出しただけですけどね｡
えっ や～だ～➡
For real? You get crushes too, Bacchus?
バッカスも恋とかするの？
ふふっ ウケる～！
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ クワッ クワッ！
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)違ぇよ バッカ野郎！
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ クワッ クワッ｡
No, you idiots!
That's hilarious!
てれてるの？ てれてるの？ ﾊﾞｯｶｽ｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)あのな➡
Are you blushing? Are you blushing, Bacchus?
No making fun of grown-ups!
大人を からかうんじゃないよ！
He's totally blushing.
(ﾊﾝｻ ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)がぁ～ がぁ～…｡
≫コン コン(ﾉｯｸ)
帰るのか？
You're leaving?
部屋まで戻れるか？
Do you know your way back to your room?
Rage of Bahamut
They are the same
and lose themselves
Cuz there are lots of roads to go
And the path suddenly seems rougher
I wanna walk straight ahead
Knock down another dream
Most broke before they ever came true
But walk this way
Get out of my way
Depends on the way you think it
To a yielding heart
the future, hope,
despair and worry all look all the same
So much that you'll turn down the truth
that lied to you that day
when you were prepared for it all.
You go your way, don't you?
But walk this way
Get out of my way
また会えたな｡
うん｡
We meet again.
かわいい｡
えっ 何？
You're adorable.
Huh!
You are always cute, but that is
especially true today.
いつもかわいいが
今日は一層かわいい｡
えっ そんな…｡ あっ｡
Really...
えっ えっ な… 何？ 何？
Oh, no.
(心の声)
≪どうしよう… こんなの 私➡
I'm going to...
I'm going to transform into a killer dragon.
凶暴な竜になっちゃう≫
≪まだ？ 背伸びじゃ届かない？≫
I can't even reach on my tiptoes?
≪ジャンプする？≫
Do I jump?
Kill them all!
皆殺しだ｡
ノー‼
クワァ～？ クワァ…｡
No!
What?
I think I just had a nightmare,
すんごい夢 見た気がするけど
思い出せない｡
but I can't remember it.
えっ？ あれ？
(ﾊﾝｻ ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)がぁ～…｡
バッカス 私の服がない｡
Bacchus! My clothes are gone!
ハンサ 服がない！
Hamsa, my clothes are gone!
(ﾊﾝｻ)
んん～ もう 着てるじゃないの｡➡
You're wearing them.
Are you sure you're awake yet?
寝ぼけてんじゃありません？
ねえ ムガロちゃん｡
Hey, Mugaro!
あっ ムガロちゃんがいない｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワァ～➡
Mugaro is gone.
What are you going on about?
いつまでも
寝ぼけてんじゃないですよ｡
でも いないよ｡
But he's not here.
クワァ～‼
バッカス！ エルがいません！➡
Bacchus! El is gone!
起きてください！
エルがいないんですよ！
Wake up! El is gone!
What?
酒 酒 酒…｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)まずいです このままでは｡
This is bad! We are going to be in so much trouble.
クワァ…｡
お酒が飲めなくなる…｡
I won't be able to drink my wine!
(ﾊﾝｻ)それどころではありません｡
これ以上の失態は➡
That's the least of our problems!
Any more mistakes and we'll be exiled for sure!
完全に神失格ですよ！
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)ああ～！
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ｡
(騎士たち)はあっ！ てやっ！
Apparently Captain Kaisar's sentence
will be carried out soon.
≪(騎士)カイザル団長の刑の執行
もうすぐだってよ｡
I wonder what's going to happen to us.
俺たち
これから どうなるんだろうな｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)おい そこの二人！➡
You two there!
Focus! We're in the middle of training!
訓練中だ！ 集中しろ｡
(２人)あっ… すいません！
My apologies!
Getting irritated isn't going to solve anything.
≫(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)イライラしても
どうにもなんないですよ｡➡
きれい事を言って
陛下に刃向かった結果がこれじゃ➡
He brought this on himself by getting
idealistic and opposing the king.
笑いも起きないっすね｡
なっ…｡
He was wrong.
(ｱﾚｻﾝﾄﾞ)
あの人は間違ってたんですよ｡
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ん？ なんだ？➡
What?
なっ… おい 何をする！
Hey! What are you doing?
副団長も捕まる気ですか！
くっ…｡
Do you want to get arrested too?
Kaisar Lidfard!
(側近)カイザル･リドファルド｡
Despite the weight of your responsibilities
as the captain of the Orleans Knights,
そなたは オルレアン騎士団の
団長という重責にありながら➡
国王陛下に対し 反逆を企て➡
you plotted against His Majesty.
更に 戦乱の混乱に乗じて脱獄し➡
In addition, you fled from prison
amidst the chaos of battle,
and repeated your crime of treason!
再び 反逆行為を繰り返した｡➡
この罪に弁解の余地なし！➡
There can be no justification for these crimes!
よって 悪魔との死闘をもって
そなたの死刑を執行する！
You are accordingly sentenced to death
by combat against this demon!
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)アザゼル｡
Azazel...
≫コン コン
なんだ？
What is it?
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)あっ エル君が たまには
お散歩に行きたいんですって｡
El said he'd like to go out and take a walk.
待て｡ 確認する｡
-Hold on, I will go check.
-Okay.
You were given permission as long
as I accompanied you. Come out.
私がついていくことで許可された｡
出て｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)寛大なご処置➡
Such generosity!
Lady Gabriel is a wise and just leader.
さすが ガブリエル様ですね｡
Where is that overly optimistic girl?
あの能天気な娘はどこ？
(門番)昨晩
部屋に戻りましたが｡
She returned to her room last night.
That seems strange.
Jeanne did not mention her returning.
≫(ﾘﾄﾞ)おかしい｡ ジャンヌは
戻ったと言っていなかった｡
あっ あれはエルじゃない！
That is not El!
ムガロちゃん どこだろ？
Where could Mugaro be?
I don't know!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)分からねぇ｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)あの様子じゃ➡
It doesn't seem like
he went to see Jeanne.
ジャンヌさんのところでも
ないでしょう｡
Mugaro was watching us the whole time when
Bacchus was talking about his exile last night.
昨日のムガロちゃん バッカスが
追放されたときの話 してたら➡
ずっと こっち見てた｡
追放じゃあねぇ！
I wasn't exiled!
エル君は
地上に戻りたがってましたねぇ｡
El did seem to want to get back to the surface.
(３人)ああ～！ ヒッポグリフ！
Hippogriff!
Lady Gabriel!
≫(ﾘﾄﾞ)ガブリエル様！
What is this commotion about?
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)なんです？ 騒々しい｡
(ﾘﾄﾞ)申し訳ありません｡➡
I beg your pardon, my lady.
ですが エルが脱走しました！
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)あっ｡
But El has escaped!
(ﾋｯﾎﾟｸﾞﾘﾌ)クゥー！
ん？
ヒッポ？
Hippo?
(ﾋｯﾎﾟｸﾞﾘﾌたち)クゥーー！
えっ!?
(ﾋｯﾎﾟｸﾞﾘﾌたち)クゥー！
Rage of Bahamut
(観客)どっちも死ね！
(観客)裏切り者！
You can both die!
Traitor!
(観客)何やってんだ！
What are you doing?
キン キン キン！
こんな所で見せ物になっているとは
お前らしくもない｡
It's not like you to let them make a spectacle of you.
ザシュ！
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)うっ！
逃げてんじゃねぇ！
みっともねぇぞ 団長！
Stop running away!
You're a disgrace, Captain!
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)なぜ 攻めてこない？
Why are you not attacking?
片手だと 何かときつくてな｡
It's hard with only one hand.
ふんっ！
Unless you want to die, kill me.
死にたくなければ 俺を殺せ｡
Bacchus, you go that way.
Okay.
Hamsa, you go that way.
Copy that.
I'll jump on Mugaro from up there.
For the timing,
when I get to that spot
it'll be, "One, two, three, go!"
≪ゴンッ！(ぶつかる音)
≪(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)痛っ！ ああっ…｡
(ﾆｰﾅ ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)ううっ…｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワァ…｡
ちょっと
タイミング 全然違うよ！
That wasn't the right timing at all!
お… お前の指示だろ！
We did exactly what you said!
いつまでも
くっついてないでよ 変態！
-Get off of me already, you pervert!
-Pervert?
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)変態!?
(ﾊﾝｻ)私たちには➡
I guess we needed words
to communicate.
言葉が必要ですね｡
あぁ～｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)ニーナ！
Nina!
ぬぅ～！
(観客たち)わあ～！
ドカッ！
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)うわっ！
(一同)おらぁ～！
(ﾌｧﾊﾞﾛ･ﾚｵｰﾈ)カイザル！
Kaisar!
キン！
殺せ！
ふざけんな！
-Kill him!
-Do it already!
早く殺せ！
(観客)遊びじゃねぇ…｡
Hurry up and kill him!
貴様に期待した俺がバカだった｡
I was stupid to ever expect anything from you.
(兵士)何をしている！➡
What are you doing?
あっ… おい こら！
Hey!
バン！
(兵士)うわっ！
バン バン！
アザゼル！
Azazel!
ボォン！
(兵士)うわっ！
ボォーン‼
(観客)どうなってんだ！
(観客)いいぞ もっとやれ！
What is going on?
Who cares! Keep going!
(観客)見えねぇじゃねぇか！
We can't see anything!
Just as I thought,
that man will not die without a fight!
やはり
あの男は ただでは死なん！
≫(兵士)警備を固めろ！
≫(兵士)逃げたヤツを追え！
-Secure the perimeter!
-Don't let them escape!
Don't run away, Mugaro!
ムガロちゃん 逃げないで！
Jeanne will be really sad if you're gone!
ムガロちゃんがいなくなったら
ジャンヌさんが悲しむよ～！
もらった！
Got you now!
あれ？ うわぁ～！
Thank you, Mugaro!
ありがと ムガロちゃん｡
You may have changed a little bit,
ちょっと
変わったかもしれないけど➡
but you're still Mugaro!
でも
ムガロちゃんはムガロちゃんだ｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)あのまま
結界に入ったら まずいですね｡
That barrier is bad news!
≫(ﾘﾄﾞ)あいつらです！
あいつらがエルを逃がしたんです｡
There they are! They are the ones who let El go!
(２人)ん？
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)バッカス➡
Bacchus, are you insane?
貴様 正気か！
えっ？ あっ あっ あの… えっ？
What?
ダメだ 殺される｡
Oh, no! They're going to kill us!
ピューッ(指笛)
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ！
≫(ﾊﾝｻ)クワァ～ クワッ クワッ！
(２人)あっ｡
Get in!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)乗れ！
グッドタイミング バッカス！
Good timing, Bacchus!
バリバリッ！
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ ﾊﾝｻ)うわぁ～～！
Those fools!
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)あのバカ者！
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)エル なぜ…｡
El... why?
あぁ～｡
あぁ～あ また最悪な形で➡
Once again, we left the land of the
gods in the worst way possible.
神界を出てしまいましたね｡
これクワァら
どうするんですクワァ？
What are we going to do now?
王都に戻る｡
(ｴﾙ)えっ？➡
We'll go back to Anatae.
王都に連れてってくれるの？
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)勘違いすんじゃねぇ｡➡
You'll take me to the capital?
Don't get the wrong idea.
If you're planning to fight the humans,
お前が人と戦う気なら
すぐに神に引き渡す｡
I'll hand you right back over to the gods.
(ｴﾙ)あっ うん！
僕は戦いたいわけじゃない｡
It's not that I want to fight.
I want to bring peace to the world.
世界を平和にしたいんだ｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)けっ｡
This is great, isn't it, Mugaro?
よかったね ムガロちゃん｡
うん｡
でも
ジャンヌさんは よかったの？
But what about Jeanne?
お母さんのためにも
僕は使命を果たす｡
I will fulfill my duty
for my mother's sake as well.
As horrible as you are
I can't help but love you
Even while I waited
That is all I felt
Ephemeral lovers, both flawed and missing pieces
We have finally become one
in this miniature garden at the edge of sorrow
Can you hear my heart speaking?
Ah, I may no longer feel
that I want to go back in time
But there are feelings, feelings, feelings
I can only feel now
I want to run away with you, dancing
just like in a fairy tale
Don't tell me it will only be this once, darling
I am on the same ark
Sha-ra-ran-la, Sha-ra-ran-la
Yeah
Cinderella step
Sha-ra-ran-la, Sha-ra-ran-la
Yeah
Cinderella step
(ﾘﾀ)おかえりなさい｡➡
Welcome back.
I'm glad you're okay.
無事でよかったわ｡
カイザル ロッキー返してよ｡
Kaisar, give me back Rocky.
Right.
(ﾘﾀ)ご苦労さま｡
Good job.
Where are you going?
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)どこへ行く？
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)貴様らと これ以上➡
This is as far as I go with you.
つるむ気はない｡
Don't worry about him.
ほっとけ｡
Azazel.
アザゼル お前の力を貸してくれ｡
血迷ったか？
Please help us.
Have you lost your mind?
シャリオス王は アナティの地下で
巨大な破壊兵器を製造していた｡
Charioce was building a giant weapon
underneath Anatae.
その威力はバハムートに匹敵する｡
Its power rivaled Bahamut's.
I wish to see how the king
plans to use the weapon
神をも退けたあの力を
王が 何に使おうとしているのか➡
that had the power to drive back the gods.
私は それを見定めたい｡
You want to save the demons, don't you?
悪魔を助けたいのだろう？➡
協力してくれ｡
Help us.
Hurry up and take that collar off already.
その首輪
早く取っちゃいなさいよ｡
I'm not taking your charity.
貴様らの施しは受けん｡
Well, I'll be off then.
ほんじゃ 俺は…｡
(ﾘﾀ)
１０年たっても ガキなままね｡
Still a brat 10 years on.
Knight Kaisar, how have you been?
I still do not have anyone to call a friend...
Occasionally...you.
Next time on Rage of Bahamut:
Virgin Soul, "Virgin Souls"
-I heard the Lord's voice!
-It's as though he's right beside you, isn't it?
But, you are?
BAHA SOUL!!
Baha baha baha soul!
Make sure to watch next time!
Sincerly,
the aristocrat, Kaisar.